

SHAKIR SULTANOV

visions.shkrsltnv.com

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- Ukrainian, S Permit
- 31.03.2000
- +41 76 454 7413
- sultanovshakir12@gmail.com
- Zurich, Switzerland
- in LinkedIn
- **GitHub**

PROFILE

I am a hard working and ambitious person with a positive mindset and a never ending desire to continuously learn and grow professionally. Along my academic and self-educational journey, I have had the opportunity to explore various areas of IT working on a variety of projects. I am passionate about further expanding my experience and skills to become a highly skilled and successful developer.

EDUCATION

09.2018 – 07.2022

Bachelor of Computer Engineering – Odesa Mechnikov National University, Odesa, Ukraine

- Programming fundamentals
- Computer Engineering fundamentals
- · Data structures and algorithms
- Computer networks
- Operating systems
- Web and mobile development

04.2024 - 07.2024

Powercoders Bootcamp - ICT Work Integration Program, Bern, Switzerland

- Foundations in HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Weekly business & social skills training (teamwork, communication, etc.)

REFERENCES

Kenneth Ritley

Prof. Dr. Kenneth Ritley, Dozent, BFH

<u>kenneth.ritley@bfh.ch</u> https://ritley.com/

+41 79 509 57 22

EXPERIENCE

BFH, Biel/Bienne Intern Fullstack | 08.2024 - present

During my one-year internship, I had the opportunity to work on a diverse range of non-commercial projects, which greatly enhanced my skills.

- Full-stack development based on project needs.
- Implement RESTful APIs and database integrations with PostgreSQL
- Experience with Docker and containerized environments.
- Business logic implementation and feature development.
- GitLab repository management and CI/CD pipeline automation.
- Worked with AI-powered solutions, including LangChain for LLM-based applications.
- Active collaboration with stakeholders and product teams.

Freelance

Frontender| 11.2022 - 07.2023

Developed the front-end for small landing websites in a freelance-like role. Gained experience in creating user-friendly and responsive interfaces

Responsible for design and frontend development

LLC "7th Kilometer" Seller-loader| 02.2018 – 01.2021

- · Responsible for loading
- Organize warehouse inventory efficiently
- Responsibly fulfill customer orders

SKILLS

Advanced

JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML, CSS
Intermediate

Vue.js, Angular, Python, FastAPI, PostgreSQL, Git, Docker

Beginner

Spring Boot

Basic

Java, C#, Android Studio, Figma, Gitlab, CI/CD

HOBBIES

Read

I love reading psychological books, books to understand life, people, and the world.

Music

Love to listen to music when I am working on something, especially violin.